Guide to the Samuel Stark Film and stage stars: photographs, 1911-1969
Department of Special Collections
- Frederick, Pauline (19, 8 signed, 1 to Walter Bartmann and to "Mr. Cotrell"), (1924,1928) (Box 6, Folder 455)
- Fredericks, Charles (2) (Box 6, Folder 456)
- Friganza, Trixie (4, 2 signed, 1 to Tom Lindsay, 1942, 1 to Langly [?], 1914) (1 o.s., signed) (Box 6, Folder 457)
- Fuller, Penny (Box 6, Folder 458)
- Furness, Betty (14) (1934,1935) (Box 6, Folder 459)
- Gable, Clark (25, 1 a photo of an ink drawing) (1935,1937), (2 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 460)
- Gahagan, Helen (5, 1 signed to Jack Sheridan, 1934) (5 o.s., 1 signed to Dave Souransky) (Box 7, Folder 461)
- Garbo, Greta (16) (1934, 1936, 1937), (2 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 462)
- Garbo, Greta ("Queen Christina", M.G.M. 1934) (10) (Box 7, Folder 463)
- Gardner, Joan (1935) (Box 7, Folder 464)
- Garfield, John (3) (Box 7, Folder 465)
- Gargan, William (7) (1934, 1935, 1936) (Box 7, Folder 466)
- Garland, Judy (31) (1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 467)
- Garner, Erroll (4) (Box 7, Folder 468)
- Garson, Greer (4), (1 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 469)
- Gateson, Marjorie (Box 7, Folder 470)
- Gaxton, William (2, 1 signed to "Dave") (Box 7, Folder 471)
- Gaynor, Janet (18) (1936,1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 472)
- Gaynor, Mitzi (Box 7, Folder 473)
- Gentle, Alice (signed to Mr. Harry Campbell) (Box 7, Folder 474)
- George, Gladys (7) (1936), (2 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 475)
- George, Grace (2) (Box 7, Folder 476)
- Gervay, Maritza (1936) (Box 7, Folder 477)
- Gibson, Kenneth (Box 7, Folder 478)
- Gibson, Virginia (Box 7, Folder 479)
- Gielgud, John (2) (1936) (Box 7, Folder 480)
- Gilbert, Billy (2) (1939) (Box 7, Folder 481)
- Gilbert, John(2 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 482)
- Gillette, Ruth, (1 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 483)
- Gilligan, Helen (1 o.s., signed to Sam Stark) (Box 7, Folder 484)
- Givot, George (1936) (Box 7, Folder 485)
- Gish, Lillian (7, 1 signed) (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 7, Folder 486)
- Glass, Gaston (3 o.s., 2 signed) (Box 7, Folder 487)
- Gleason, James (4, 1 autograph)(1936,1937) (Box 7, Folder 488)
- Goddard, Paulette (14)(1936, 1940) (Box 7, Folder 489)
- Gombell, Minna (Box 7, Folder 490)
- Gomez, S. Thomas (Sabino Thomas) (61 photos, 1 color; 4 sets of contact prints, 1 set with negs; clipping from Long Island Sunday Press, 10/14/56, 2 autograph, 3 signed but not by STG) (1925, 1929, 1938, 1944, 1946, 1948, 1949, 1960, 1961, 1967) (Box 7, Folder 491)
- Gordon, Huntley (Box 7, Folder 492)
- Grable, Betty (6) (1935, 1936) (Box 7, Folder 493)
- Graham, Martha (13) (Box 7, Folder 494)
- Martha Graham Dance Group (2) (Box 7, Folder 495)
- Graham, Ronnie (Box 7, Folder 496)
- Grahame, Margot (Box 7, Folder 497)
- Grant, Cary (5) (1935) (Box 7, Folder 498)
- Granville, Bonita (7, 1 autograph, 1 signed[?]) (1936) (Box 7, Folder 499)
- Graves, Ralph (Box 7, Folder 500)
- Gray, Billy (2) (Box 7, Folder 501)
- Gray, Dolores (Box 7, Folder 502)
- Gray, Gilda (Box 7, Folder 503)
- Grayco, Helen (Box 7, Folder 504)
- Green, Bennett (signed, to "Sam") (Box 7, Folder 505)
- Green, Harry (1 o.s., signed to Dave Souransky) (Box 7, Folder 506)
- Greene, Richard (Box 7, Folder 507)
- Greenstreet, Sydney (Box 7, Folder 508)
- Greenwood, Charlotte(2 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 509)
- Grenfell, Joyce (10) (Box 7, Folder 510)
- Grey, Virginia (Box 7, Folder 511)
- Griffith, Corinne (2, 1 signed) (Box 7, Folder 512)
- Griffith, Virginia (Box 7, Folder 513)
- Guinan, Texas (4 o.s., 3 signed) (Box 7, Folder 514)
- Guizar, Tito (Box 7, Folder 515)
- Gurie, Sigrid (1937) (Box 7, Folder 516)
- Gwenn, Edmund (Box 7, Folder 517)
- Hackett, James (1936) (Box 7, Folder 518)
- Haden, Sara (Box 7, Folder 519)
- Haines, William (6) (Box 7, Folder 520)
- Hale, Alan (7) (1934, 1935, 1936) (Box 7, Folder 521)
- Haley, Jacke (5) (1936, 1937) (Box 7, Folder 522)
- Halliday, Bob (signed, to "Wess") (Box 7, Folder 523)
- Halliday, Helen (Box 7, Folder 524)
- Halliday, John (1935) (Box 7, Folder 525)
- Hampden, Walter (5 photos, 3 signed, all to Tom Gomez; 1 clipping marked "Cover of 'Time', March 4 1929", 1 newspaper clipping: painting of WH as Cyrano de Bergerac) (Box 7, Folder 526)
- Hamilton, Mahlon (Box 7, Folder 527)
- Hardie, Russell (Box 7, Folder 528)
- Harding, Ann (17) (1936, 1938), (2 o.s., signed) (Box 7, Folder 529)
- Hardwicke, Cedric, Sir (signed, to Isalba[?] Bartmann) (Box 7, Folder 530)
- Hardy, Sam (2, 1 autograph) (Box 7, Folder 531)
- Harlow, Jean (24, photos, 1 of a charcoal[?] drawing)(1935), (1 o.s.) (Box 7, Folder 532)
- Harris, George (2, 1 signed, 1931, to "Dave") (Box 7, Folder 533)
- Harris, Julie (Box 7, Folder 534)
- Hart, William S(5, 2 signed), (1949) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hasso, Signe (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hatfield, Lansing (3, 1 signed, 1938) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Havel, Morton and Arthur (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Havber, Phyllis (3, 1 signed, to Joe Laurie, 1921) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hawkins, Erick (see Martha Graham) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hawkins, Jack (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayakowa, Sessue (4, 3 signed, to H. Janss and B.G. Willis) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayden, Melissa (6) (dancer, NYC ballet) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Haydon, Julie (2, 1932) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayes, Helen (12 photos, 1 neg) (1936, 1937, 1963) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayes, Margaret (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayes, Peter L. (3) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayward, Louis (6) (1935, 1936) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hayworth, Rita (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Healey, Frank (signed, to "Harry and the boys", 2-20-04) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Healy, Ted (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Heath, T.K., James McIntyre, George Primrose (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Heckart, Eileen (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Heirs, Walter (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Heming, Violet (signed, 1944)(2 o.s.) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Henie, Sonja (skater) (17) (1936, 1937) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hepburn, Katharine (4) (1937) (3 o.s.) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Herbert, Evelyn (signed, 1925-1935?) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Herbert, Holmes (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Herbert, Hugh (8) (1936, 1937) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hersholt, Jean (11, 1 photo of accident report, 1923) (1935) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hervey, Irene (10) (1936, 1936) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hibbard, Edna (1929) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hightower, Rosabella (ballet dancer) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hiller, Wendy (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hinsdell, Oliver (1 o.s., signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hobart, Rose (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hobson, Valerie (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hoctor, Harriet, (1 o.s.) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hoffa, Portland (1938) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Holland, Jack, and June Knight (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Holloway, Stanley (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Holloway, Sterling (5) (1935, 1939, 1940) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Holme, Celeste (see Vera Allen) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Holt, Jack (2) (1929) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hope, Bob (1940) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hopkins, Miriam (9) (1934, 1935, 1937) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hopper, DeWolf (1 o.s., signed to Jim Laurie) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hopper, Hedda (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hopple, Mary (3) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Horton, E.E. (Edward Everett) (11, 3 s; 2 to David Suransky) (1932, '35, '37, '41) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- House, Billy (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Houston, George (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Howard, John (5) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Howard, Leslie (5)(1932-33, 1935), (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Howard, Trevor (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hoxie, Jack (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hudson, Rock (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hughes, Lloyd (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hulette, Gladys (signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hull, Henry (3), (1 o.s.) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hull, Shelley (signed, 1918) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hull, Warren (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hulten, Vivi-Anne (ice-skater) (14) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hume, Benita (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Humphries, Dorothy (8) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hunt, Marsha (9) (1935, 1936, 1937) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hunter, Diane (1934) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hunter, Ian (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hussey, Ruth (3) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Huston, Virginia (signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Huston, Walter (8) (1934, 1935, 1936) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hyams, John and Leila McIntyre Hyams (signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Hytten, Olaf (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Inescort, Frieda (signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jacobson, Irving (Box 8, Folder 535)
- James, Claire (Miss California)(1938) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- James, Harry (Box 8, Folder 535)
- James, Will (1933) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Janis, Elsie (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Janssen, David (and George Takei) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jeffreys, Anne (2) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jenkins, Allen (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jessel, Patricia (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jessell, George (3) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jewell, Isabel (3) (1936), (1 o.s., signed to Sam Stark) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Johnson, Kay (1 o.s., signed to Dave Suransky) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Johnson, Osa (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Johnson, Rita (7) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jolson, Al (10) (1935, 1936) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jones, Allan (8, 1 signed) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Jones, Buck (5) (1932, 1935, 1936) (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Harron, John (Box 8, Folder 535)
- Joy, Leatrice (6, 2 signed) (1922, 1926) (Box 9, Folder 624)
- Joyce, Alice (2) (Box 9, Folder 625)
- Karloff, Boris (6) (1935, 1936, 1942) (Box 9, Folder 626)
- Karns, Roscoe (5) (1933, 1936) (Box 9, Folder 627)
- Kaye, Danny (1970) (Box 9, Folder 628)
- Kaye, Nora (ballet dancer) (6) (Box 9, Folder 629)
- Keating, Fred (5, 4 signed) (Box 9, Folder 630)
- Keaton, Buster (2) (Box 9, Folder 631)
- Keeler, Ruby (7) (1935) (Box 9, Folder 632)
- Keenan, Frank (Box 9, Folder 633)
- Keith, Ian (6, 1 signed) (1932) (Box 9, Folder 634)
- Keith-Johnson, Colin (Box 9, Folder 635)
- Kellerman, Annette (signed, 1924 to J.M. (?) Campbell) (Box 9, Folder 636)
- Kelly, Nancy (Box 9, Folder 637)
- Kelly, Patsy (1935, 1936) (Box 9, Folder 638)
- Kelly, Tommy (child star) (Box 9, Folder 639)
- Kelly, Walter (signed, to Harry Campbell) (Box 9, Folder 640)
- Kennedy, Madge (2, 1 signed) (1913/1923) (Box 9, Folder 641)
- Kenyon, Doris (signed) (Box 9, Folder 642)
- Kenyon, Gwen (1938) (Box 9, Folder 643)
- Kenyon, Nancy (Box 9, Folder 644)
- Kerr, Deborah (Box 9, Folder 645)
- Kerry, Norman (Box 9, Folder 646)
- Keyes, Evelyn (Box 9, Folder 647)
- Kibbee, Guy (5) (1935, 1936) (Box 9, Folder 648)
- Kiepura, Jan (1935) (Box 9, Folder 649)
- Kilburn, Terry (child star?) (Box 9, Folder 650)
- King, Charles (Box 9, Folder 651)
- King, Dennis (Box 9, Folder 652)
- Kirkbride, Betty (Box 9, Folder 653)
- Kirkwood, James, (1 o.s.) (Box 9, Folder 654)
- Kirove, Ivan (ballet dancer) (Box 9, Folder 655)
- Kirsten, Dorothy (Box 9, Folder 656)
- Kitt, Eartha (2) (1952) (Box 9, Folder 657)
- Kneff, Hildegarde (Box 9, Folder 658)
- Korber, Hilda (see Ms 287:2 photos, 2 typescripts) (Box 9, Folder 659)
- Korff, Arnold (Box 9, Folder 660)
- Korjus, Miliza (2) (Box 9, Folder 661)
- Krassovska, Nathalie (ballet dancer) (2) (Box 9, Folder 662)
- Kriza, John (see Alicia Alonzo) (Box 9, Folder 663)
- Kruger, Otto (6, 1 signed) (Box 9, Folder 664)
- Kulker, Henry (1934) (Box 9, Folder 665)
- Lackaye, Welton (signed, 1902) (Box 9, Folder 666)
- Lahr, Bert (2) (1947) (Box 9, Folder 667)
- Lake, Alice (1915) (Box 9, Folder 668)
- Lake, Arthur (3) (Box 9, Folder 669)
- Lake, Veronica (2) (Box 9, Folder 670)
- La Marr, Barbara (Box 9, Folder 671)
- Lamarr, Hedy(2 o.s.) (Box 9, Folder 672)
- Lambert, Gracie (2) (Box 9, Folder 673)
- Lamour, Dorothy (11) (1936, 1937, 1938, 1939) (Box 9, Folder 674)
- Lane, Lola (Box 9, Folder 675)
- Lane, Priscilla and Rosemary (7) (1938) (4 o.s.) (Box 9, Folder 676)
- Langan, Glenn (signed) (1941-42?) (Box 9, Folder 677)
- La Plante, Laura (3) (Box 9, Folder 678)
- La Rue, Jack (1935) (Box 9, Folder 679)
- Laudi, Ellesa (2) (Box 9, Folder 680)
- Laudis, Cullen (Box 9, Folder 681)
- Latimer, Louise (1936) (Box 9, Folder 682)
- Lauder, Sir Harry (3) (Box 9, Folder 683)
- Laughton, Charles (8) (1932, 1934) (Box 9, Folder 684)
- Laurel and Hardy (Stan Laurel and Oliver Hardy) (8) (1936) (Box 9, Folder 685)
- Laurie, Joe Jr(1892-1954) (Box 9, Folder 686)
  (9, 2 s; 1 orig cartoon, W.A. Carbson) (pre-1920, 1942, 1946, 1949) (3 o.s.)
- Lawford, Betty (Box 9, Folder 687)
- Lawrence, Bob (3) (Box 9, Folder 688)
- Lawrence, Gertrude (9) (3 o.s., 2 signed) (Box 9, Folder 689)
- Laye, Evelyn (4) (Box 9, Folder 690)
- Layne, Rickie (Box 9, Folder 691)
- Leclercq, Tanaquil (see also Andre Eglensky file) (ballet dancer) (5) (Box 9, Folder 692)
- Lederer, Francis (5) (1936, 1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 9, Folder 693)
- Lee, Anna (3) (1936) (Box 9, Folder 694)
- Lee, Betsy (1928) (Box 9, Folder 695)
- Lee, Billy (child star) (signed, 1936) (Box 9, Folder 696)
- Lee, Frankie (child star) (Box 9, Folder 697)
- Lee,Gwen (1 o.s., signed) (Box 9, Folder 698)
- Lee, Lila (Box 9, Folder 699)
- Leeds, Andrea (3) (1936, 1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 9, Folder 700)
- Leeds, Marian (Box 9, Folder 701)
- Le Galliene, Eva (3) (Box 9, Folder 702)
- Leiber, Fritz (4) (1936, 1937) (Box 9, Folder 703)
- Leigh, Vivian (6) (1939) (Box 9, Folder 704)
- Leontovich, Eugenie (signed) (3) (1930) (Box 9, Folder 705)
- Le Roy, "Baby" (1933) (child star) (Box 9, Folder 706)
- Leslie, Gladys (Box 9, Folder 707)
- Lester, Edwin (3) (1975) (2 newspaper articles, letter) (Box 9, Folder 708)
- Lewis, Ted (singer, dancer) (Box 9, Folder 709)
- Lifar, Serge (see Tamara Toumanova file) (Box 9, Folder 710)
- Lillie, Beatrice (Box 10, Folder 711)
- Lindsay, Margaret (3) (1936) (Box 10, Folder 712)
- Lindfors, Viveca (Box 10, Folder 713)
- Livingstone, Mary (1937) (Box 10, Folder 714)
- Lloyd, Alice (signed) (1921) (Box 10, Folder 715)
- Lloyd, Doris (2) (Box 10, Folder 716)
- Lloyd, Gladys (2) (Box 10, Folder 717)
- Lloyd, Harold (5) (1932) (signed-reproduced) (Box 10, Folder 718)
- Lockhart, Gene (4) (1936) (Box 10, Folder 719)
- Loftus, Cecilia (4) (1939) (Box 10, Folder 720)
- Lord, Pauline (12) (1934, 1935, 1936, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 721)
- Lord, Pauline (Box 10, Folder 722)
- Lorimer, Louise (Box 10, Folder 723)
- Lorrain, Louise (Box 10, Folder 724)
- Lorre, Peter (4) (1937, 1941) (signed-reproduced) (Box 10, Folder 725)
- Losch, Tilly (3) (1936, 1937) (Box 10, Folder 726)
- Louise, Anita (6) (1936, 1937) (Box 10, Folder 727)
- Love, Bessie (3) (Box 10, Folder 728)
- Love, Montague (signed) (Box 10, Folder 729)
- Lowe, Edmund (8) (1936) (signed) (Box 10, Folder 730)
- Loy, Myrna (37) (1930, 1936, 1937, 1949) (6 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 731)
- Ludwig, Rose (Box 10, Folder 732)
- Lugosi, Bela (2) (signed) (Box 10, Folder 733)
- Lukas, Paul (Box 10, Folder 734)
- Lund, John, (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 735)
- Lunt, Alfred (2) (signed) (Box 10, Folder 736)
- Lupino, Ida (12) (1934, 1935, 1936, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 737)
- Lynde, Paul (1952) (Box 10, Folder 738)
- Lynn, Diana (1947) (Box 10, Folder 739)
- Lynn, Jeffrey (Box 10, Folder 740)
- Lynn, Patricia (Box 10, Folder 741)
- Lyon, Ben (1934) (signed) ( photo of children including one of his) (Box 10, Folder 742)
- Lys, Lya, (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 743)
- Lytell, Bert (5) (signed) (Box 10, Folder 744)
- MacDonald, Jeanette (27) (1937) (9 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 745)
- MacDowell, Melbourne (1902) (Box 10, Folder 746)
- MacMahon, Aline (6) (1956) (Box 10, Folder 747)
- MacMurray, Fred (6) (1935, 1936, 1941, 1947) (Box 10, Folder 748)
- MacPhail, Agnes (Box 10, Folder 749)
- McAvoy, May (signed-reproduced) (Box 10, Folder 750)
- McCabe, Sara Ann (3) (Box 10, Folder 751)
- McCoy, Mildred (Box 10, Folder 752)
- McCrea, Joel (3) (1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 753)
- McDaniel, Hattie (Box 10, Folder 754)
- McDonald, Marie (Box 10, Folder 755)
- McGlynn, Frank (Box 10, Folder 756)
- McGowan, Roxy (Box 10, Folder 757)
- McGuire, Dorothy (1942) (Box 10, Folder 758)
- McGuire, Mickey (2) (child star) (Box 10, Folder 759)
- McHugh, Frank (2) (1936) (Box 10, Folder 760)
- McIntosh, Burr (1936) (signed) (Box 10, Folder 761)
- McKay, Scott (2) (Box 10, Folder 762)
- McLaglen, Victor (1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 763)
- McLane, Barton (1936) (Box 10, Folder 764)
- McNeill, Claudia (Box 10, Folder 765)
- Mack, Charles (2) (1929) (signed) (Box 10, Folder 766)
- Mack, Helen (2) (1934, 1935) (Box 10, Folder 767)
- Magallanes, Nicholas (ballet dancer) (Box 10, Folder 768)
- Main, Marjorie (1947) (Box 10, Folder 769)
- Malina, Luba, (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 770)
- Malo, Gina (Box 10, Folder 771)
- Man, Lila (Box 10, Folder 772)
- Manero, Jose (see Ruby Asquith and Lois Treadwell) (Box 10, Folder 773)
- Manning, Hope(2 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 774)
- Manning, Irene, (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 775)
- Mantell, Robert (Box 10, Folder 776)
- Maracci, Carmelita (Box 10, Folder 777)
- Marc & Madona (Box 10, Folder 778)
- Marceau, Marcel (6) (Box 10, Folder 779)
- March, Fredric (5) (also see Janet Gaynor) (Box 10, Folder 780)
- March twins (1930's) (Box 10, Folder 781)
- Margo (3) (actress and dancer) (Box 10, Folder 782)
- Markova, Alicia (ballet dancer) (Box 10, Folder 783)
- Marks, Joe (Box 10, Folder 784)
- Marracci, Livia (Box 10, Folder 785)
- Marsh, Marian (1936) (Box 10, Folder 786)
- Marshal, Alan (Box 10, Folder 787)
- Marshall, Armina, (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 788)
- Marshall, Brenda, (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 789)
- Marshall, Everett (Box 10, Folder 790)
- Marshall, Herbert (5) (1935, 1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 10, Folder 791)
- Marshe, Vera (4) (Box 10, Folder 792)
- Martin, Marion (1939) (Box 10, Folder 793)
- Martin, Mary (8) (1939, 1940) (Box 10, Folder 794)
- Marx Brothers (9) (1933, 1936, 1937) (Box 10, Folder 795)
- Mason, Melissa (2) (Box 10, Folder 796)
- Mason, Reginald (Box 11, Folder 797)
- Mason, Shirley (2) (Box 11, Folder 798)
- Massey, Ilona (2) (Box 11, Folder 799)
- Massey, Raymond (2) (Box 11, Folder 800)
- Mathis, Johnny (Box 11, Folder 801)
- Maxwell, Edwin (Box 11, Folder 802)
- Mayhew, Kate (Box 11, Folder 803)
- Meadows, Jayne, (1974, 1975, 1976), (poster, biography sheet, letter from Steve Allen, article plus 13 photocopies) (Box 11, Folder 804)
- Meek, Donald (Box 11, Folder 805)
- Meeker, Marie (1927) (Box 11, Folder 806)
- Meighan, Thomas (3) (signed, reproduced) (Box 11, Folder 807)
- Melville, Emelie, (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 808)
- Menjou, Adolphe (5), (1936, 1937) (also see Janet Gaynor) (Box 11, Folder 809)
- Menken, Helen (2), (1936) (Box 11, Folder 810)
- Mercer, Meryl (Box 11, Folder 811)
- Meredith, Burgess (1937) (Box 11, Folder 812)
- Merivale, John (Box 11, Folder 813)
- Merivale, Philip (2) (Box 11, Folder 814)
- Merkel, Una (18) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 815)
- Merman, Ethel (signed, reproduced) (Box 11, Folder 816)
- Mestayer, Harry (Box 11, Folder 817)
- Metaxa, Georges (1936) (Box 11, Folder 818)
- Michael, Gertrude (1934) (Box 11, Folder 819)
- Milberg, Barbara (dancer) (2) (Box 11, Folder 820)
- Milland, Ray (6) (1936, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 821)
- Miller, Helene, (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 822)
- Miller, Henry (writer), (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 823)
- Miller, Marilyn (12), (signed), (1915, 1918, 1921, 1922, 1924, 1931), (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 824)
- Minter, Mary (2) (signed) (Box 11, Folder 825)
- Miranda, Carmen, (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 826)
- Mitchel, Thomas (4) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 827)
- Mix, Tom (4) (Box 11, Folder 828)
- Moncion, Francisco (3) (ballet dancer) (Box 11, Folder 829)
- Monroe, Marilyn (1954) (Box 11, Folder 830)
- Montand, Yves (6) (1962) (Box 11, Folder 831)
- Montgomery, Douglass (2) (signed) (Box 11, Folder 832)
- Montgomery, Robert (11) (1936) (Box 11, Folder 833)
- Mooney, Tom (Box 11, Folder 834)
- Moore, Collen (2), (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 835)
- Moore, Florence (Box 11, Folder 836)
- Moore, Grace (3) (1936) (Box 11, Folder 837)
- Moore, Victor (5) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 838)
- Moran, Polly (Box 11, Folder 839)
- Moreno, Antonio (3) (Box 11, Folder 840)
- Morey, Harry (Box 11, Folder 841)
- Morgan, Claudia (Box 11, Folder 842)
- Morgan, Frank (5) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 843)
- Morgan, Helen (3) (Box 11, Folder 844)
- Morgan, Ralph (2) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 845)
- Morison, Patricia (2) (Box 11, Folder 846)
- Morley, Karen (4) (1936, 1937) (Box 11, Folder 847)
- Morri, Ann (Box 11, Folder 848)
- Morris, Chester (4) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 849)
- Morris, Mary (2) (Box 11, Folder 850)
- Morris, Wayne (4) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 851)
- Morrison, Louis (2) (1910) (signed) (Box 11, Folder 852)
- Morrow, Doretta (Box 11, Folder 853)
- Mowbray, Alan (2) (1 o.s.signed to Dave Suransky) (Box 11, Folder 854)
- Mulhall, Jack, (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 855)
- Muni, Paul (8) (1935, 1937, 1940) (Box 11, Folder 856)
- Munro, David (Box 11, Folder 857)
- Munson, Ona (Box 11, Folder 858)
- Murphy, George (6) (1937, 1940) (Box 11, Folder 859)
- Murray, John, (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 860)
- Murray, Mae (2) (1 o.s., signed) (Box 11, Folder 861)
- Myers, Carmel (Box 11, Folder 862)
- Myrtil, Odette (3) (Box 11, Folder 863)
- Nagel, Conrad (2) (1938) (4 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 864)
- Naismith, Lawrence (1964) (Box 11, Folder 865)
- Nash, Mary (signed) (Box 11, Folder 866)
- Nazimova, Alla (2) (1928) (Box 11, Folder 867)
- Neagle, Anna (7) (1940) (Box 11, Folder 868)
- Negri, Pola (2) (1939) (Box 11, Folder 869)
- Nelson, Peter - see Asquith file, see Treadwell, Louis file (Box 11, Folder 870)
- Nielsen, Alice (1 o.s., signed) (Box 11, Folder 871)
- Nielson Twins (5) (1926) (Box 11, Folder 872)
- Nilson, Anna (Box 11, Folder 873)
- Niven, David (7) (1935, 1967) (Box 11, Folder 874)
- Nixon, Marian (2) (Box 11, Folder 875)
- Nolan, Doris (1936) (Box 11, Folder 876)
- Nolan, Kathy (2) (Box 11, Folder 877)
- Nolan, Lloyd (3) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 878)
- Nolan, Mary (Box 11, Folder 879)
- Norworth, Jack (2) (signed) (Box 11, Folder 880)
- Novarro, Ramon (9) (1931, (signed) (Box 11, Folder 881)
- Nugent, Eddie (3) (1935), (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 882)
- Mutez, Lola (Box 11, Folder 883)
- Oakie, Jack (8) (1937) (Box 11, Folder 884)
- Oaklay, Florence (signed, reproduced) (Box 11, Folder 885)
- Oakland, Vivien, (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 886)
- Oberon, Merle (4), (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 887)
- O'Brien, George (Box 11, Folder 888)
- O'Brien, Pat (9) (1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 11, Folder 889)
- O'Brien-Moore, Erin (3) (1935) (Box 12, Folder 890)
- O'Connor, Una (1944) (Box 12, Folder 891)
- O'Hara, Fiske (Box 12, Folder 892)
- O'Hara, Peggy (Box 12, Folder 893)
- Oland, Warner, (1 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 894)
- Olivier, Lawrence (3) (Box 12, Folder 895)
- Olson & Johnson (3) (Box 12, Folder 896)
- Oliver, Edna May (3 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 12, Folder 897)
- Olmstead, Gertrude (1 o.s., signed) (Box 12, Folder 898)
- O'Neil, Nance (2) (Box 12, Folder 899)
- O'Neil, Sally, (2) (Box 12, Folder 900)
- O'Neill, Henry (Box 12, Folder 901)
- O'Neill, Sherry (3) (Box 12, Folder 902)
- O'Sullivan, Maureen (25) (1936, 1937) (Box 12, Folder 903)
- Oneto, Richard (Box 12, Folder 904)
- Operti, LeRoi, (14), (1954, 1955) (Box 12, Folder 905)
- Our Gang - Players (27) (1935, 1936) (autographed, reproduced) (Box 12, Folder 906)
- Ouspenskaya, Marie (1936) (Box 12, Folder 907)
- Overman, Lynn (1937) (Box 12, Folder 908)
- Owen, Reginald (1930), (autographed) (Box 12, Folder 909)
- Page, Anita (5), (1 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 910)
- Page, Gale (2), (1 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 911)
- Page, Tamara (2) (Box 12, Folder 912)
- Palance, Jack (Box 12, Folder 913)
- Pall, Gloria (2) (fact sheet plus note to Mr. Stark), (1958) (Box 12, Folder 914)
- Pallette, Eugene (Box 12, Folder 915)
- Palmer, Maria (Box 12, Folder 916)
- Parker, Barnett (2) (Box 12, Folder 917)
- Parker, Cecilia (2) (Box 12, Folder 918)
- Parker, Jean (8) (1936) (Box 12, Folder 919)
- Patrick, Gail (4) (1936) (Box 12, Folder 920)
- Payne, John (3) (1937, 1964), (2 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 921)
- Peabody, Eddie (2) (autographed) (Box 12, Folder 922)
- Pearson, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 923)
- Peck, Gregory (Box 12, Folder 924)
- Pendleton, Nat (3) (Box 12, Folder 925)
- Penner, Joe (4) (1934, 1936) (Box 12, Folder 926)
- Pennington, Ann (Box 12, Folder 927)
- Perkins, Osgood (Box 12, Folder 928)
- Perkins, Walter E, (autographed) (Box 12, Folder 929)